

Your own direction

【 (+82) 10-9030-1843 | ■ email | ☐ regalk13 | In link

"Be the change that you want to see in the world."

| S | | m | m | a | r | V |
|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|
| • | ч | | | a | | v |

Current Software Engineer. 4+ years experience specializing in the backend development, infrastructure automation, and computer hacking/security. Super nerd who loves Vim and Linux, and enjoys to customize all of the development environment. Interested in devising a better problem-solving method for challenging tasks, and learning new technologies and tools if the need arises.

Work Experience

Freelancer Remote

Jan.2020 - dec.2021 SOFTWARE ENGINEER

- · Working on multiple projects that require different types of implementation languages and technologies.
- Python, Java, C, C++, SQL, NO-SQL

Writing _____

Some guides of developers

Daily.dev

• You're writing something? tell it here

mar.2021 - PRESENT

Personal Projects and interests _____

2020 **Own honors**, Explain a little

Remote

Education

Institution

Locate

EDUCATION

Jan. 2020 - Nov. 2021 • Gives me experience with programming and computer basics.